# JUNYAO WANG

 $\blacksquare$  wjyyy1@whu.edu.cn  $\cdot$   $\$  (+86) 183-710-16824  $\cdot$   $\$  https://juny.wang  $\cdot$   $\$  blog:wjyyy.top

### **₩** BIOGRAPHY

Junyao Wang is a junior undergraduate in Computer School and Hongyi Honor College of Wuhan University.

He takes part in ACM-ICPC training and contests, awarding gold medal in Asia regional contest and silver medal in Asia-east continent final. And he attends the lab focusing on biomedical image analysis in Computer School directed by Prof. Feng LIU and Dr. Fei LUO. He has had a program experience since High School for Olympiad in Informatics.

He is now an intern research assistant in Hong Kong University of Science and Technology(Guangzhou).

## **EDUCATION**

### Xiangyang No.4 High School, Xiangyang, China

2017 - 2020

High School Student

### Wuhan University, Wuhan, China

2020 - 2024

B.E. in Computer Science (CS) of Hongyi Honor College

GPA: 3.83/4.00 with New Youth Pacemaker Award of the Honor College in 2023(Top 1% students)

Comprehensive Performance Measurements(second year): Rank 10/132

Leader of ACM-ICPC group of Hongyi Honor College in Wuhan University.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Large Language Model Privacy Extraction Attack.

2023 – Present

Research Assistant Supervisor: Prof. Hao LIU

Brief introduction: Research on attacking and defense the privacy information of training data of LLMs.

# **Evolutionary modeling of lung nodules based on high-resolution medical images.** 2020 – Present

Undergraduate Leader Supervisor: Prof. Feng LIU

Brief introduction: Research on medical image of CT or MRI images of lung and brain for segmentation and registration.

- Implement SOTA of medical image processing: U-net, ViT, TransUnet and so on.
- Experiment on segmentation and registration: VoxelMorph, ViT-V-Net, TransMorph and find the potential to improve the performance. (Improve the DSC by 0.5%, paper in draft)
- Assist in paper review from APBC2023(Asia Pacific Bioinformatics Conference).
- Combining Fuzzy theory into medical image processing.

[1] **J. Wang**, F. Liu, S. Shu, G. Tao, and F. Zhou, "Unsupervised brain MRI image registration based on hybrid ViT and convolutional U-net," *Scientific Reports*, under review.

### RISC-V five-stage pipeline CPU design.

May. 2022 – July. 2022

Verilog and FPGA project Individual Projects

Brief introduction: Using Verilog to simulate a CPU with interactive and graphics on FPGA board. % https://github.com/wjy-yy/cpu

- Single-cycle and Pipeline CPU design in RISC-V framework.
- Assembly programming and debugging on Venus platform for testing the hazard detection and interrupts of self-designed CPU.
- Programming simple games with assembly instructions and display via VGA on FPGA development boards.

### Guangzhou Code Island Information Technology Co.

Jan. 2021 – Present

Part-time Programming Assistant

Brief introduction: Teaching Olympics in Informatics and Programming Competitions.

- Teaching basic algorithm: graph theory, data structure, math theory.
- Online judge platform management, including function adjustment and students' code analysis.
- Produce practice questions and tests for competitions, helping students get higher grades is USACO and National Olympiad in Informatics in Province etc.

### ♥ Honors and Awards

| New Youth Pacemaker Award (Top 1%), Hongyi Honor College of Wuhan University  | June, 2023 |
|---|------------|
| Shenzhen Stock Exchange Prize(Top 5%), Wuhan University   | 2021-2022  |
| Wang-Guoqi Luo-Jinghua Prize(Top 5%~10%), Wuhan University  | 2020-2021  |
| Second-class Scholarship in Wuhan University (Top 7%), Wuhan University   | 2021-2022  |
| Second-class Scholarship in Wuhan University (Top 6%), Wuhan University   | 2020-2021  |
| Outstanding Teaching Assistant (9 out of 76), Computer Science School of Wuhan University                           | July, 2023 |
| Gold Medal, ranks 24 out of 511 teams, International Collegiate Programming Contest(ACM-ICPC) Yinchuan              |            |
| Regional Contest  | May, 2021  |
| Gold Medal, 10 <sup>th</sup> Prize, ranks 10 out of 543 participants, China Computer Federation-Collegiate Computer |            |
| Systems & Programming Contest   | Dec. 2022  |
| Silver Medal, International Collegiate Programming Contest(ACM-ICPC) Asia-East Continent Final Contest              |            |
| -   | July, 2022 |
| Gold Medal, China Collegiate Computing Contest-Group Programming Ladder Tournament                                  | May, 2021  |
| Gold Medal, Champion out of 98 teams, Hubei Province Collegiate Programming Contest                                 | May, 2021  |
| Bronze Medal, China Collegiate Programming Contest  | Oct, 2021  |
| Bronze Medal, top of Bronze list, National Olympiad in Informatics(NOI)   | Aug, 2019  |

### SKILLS

- Programming Languages: C++ > Python > Java
- Platform: Windows/Mac OS
- China Computer Federation Certificated Software Professional (CCF-CSP) 400/500 (Top 0.46%)
- CET-4: 615/710, CET-6: 580/710
- IELTS(Acdemic): 6.5(5.5)

#### i Miscellaneous

- Blog: https://www.wjyyy.top/
- GitHub: https://github.com/wjy-yy/
- Assistant Class Teacher at Hongyi Honor College of Wuhan University
- Teaching Assistant of Algorithm Design and Analysis Course in Computer School, Wuhan University
- Being in Hongyi College, which is an honor college in Wuhan University
- Assigning problems in Hubei Collegiate Program Contest and other contests
- China Computer Federation(CCF) propagandize in % website and % wechat platform(Chinese version).